{
    "id": "2af5db24174045d3912df7465320cc04",
    "title": "Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Each of the four boys …………………… clever.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after each and every.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "574ca01215024309bf57d01f540e4230"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither of them …………………… there.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after each either and neither.",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "80f581f81a774c568a7d85c9961f55e5"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… books are lost.",
            "description": "Possessives are Group A determiners. They cannot go before Group B determiners (all, some, any, either, neither etc.)",
            "answers": [
                "My all",
                "All my",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3802a3fafdbc45a1bd19842630aae359"
        },
        {
            "question": "The two brothers quarreled with ……………………….",
            "description": "Each other is used to talk about two people or things.",
            "answers": [
                "one another",
                "each other"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "770b7f5d6ca04ec18a61a62ada89ae54"
        },
        {
            "question": "Your need is greater than …………………..",
            "description": "Mine means my need here. ",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "me",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f020d36946004c4b98223f682eb535d8"
        },
        {
            "question": "John and …………………… are friends.",
            "description": "Pronouns used as subjects should be in their subject form.",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b075430a7a4040518cfc0c5c5c40be55"
        },
        {
            "question": "Rahul and I …………………… cousins.",
            "description": "When the subject is made up of two or more singular nouns, the verb should be plural.",
            "answers": [
                "am",
                "are",
                "is"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2f947d44c9f94fb4ba58005c9fde9ff3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is older than …………………… am.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me",
                "myself"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "acb2b44e86d445daa9dd811be177737b"
        },
        {
            "question": "None of us …………………….. seen him.",
            "description": "Singular verbs are more common after none.",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3f5df1e9278947daa3f2d7b99fee3f05"
        },
        {
            "question": "My essay is better than …………………..",
            "description": "Yours means your essay.",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4ab0ac11e4c045d5885c5c3221a9374f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Every light …………………… out.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after every.",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ab8ce722c51a451c97a694d346603df2"
        },
        {
            "question": "That boy of ……………………… has broken my window again.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "350225a61b6b4e2e9173a23869851697"
        }
    ]
}